KEVIN WASHINGTON

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

INFO

ADDRESS

Maceió/AL

PHONE

+55 82 98221-4242

EMAIL

kevin@kevinws.com

LINKS

<u>GitHub</u>

LinkedIn

Personal website

SKILLS

Angular, Node and Vue

 \bullet

HTML5, CSS3 and JS

 \bullet

Git, GitHub and GitLab

• • • • •

LESS and SASS

• • • • 0

Graphic design and UX design

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

Eslint and JSLint

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Jasmine and Karma

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

React

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Django, Laravel and Rails

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Ionic and Xamarin

• 0 0 0 0

LANGUAGES

Portuguese

• • • •

English

• • • 0 0

PROFILE

Front-end developer specialized in developing interfaces focused on user experience. I have experience with several programming languages and frameworks for web / mobile development and design. At the moment, I am a member of the Scientific Computing and Visualization Laboratory at the Federal University of Alagoas (LCCV / UFAL).

Computer Engineering student (UFAL), drone pilot and information security enthusiast - I also plant grapefruits and train pigeons in my spare time.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Developer, LCCV/UFAL

Maceió/AL

Aug 2019 — Present

Developer and researcher with emphasis on well engineering.

Front-end Developer, AVNIDA

Maceió/AL

Jun 2018 — Dec 2018

Front-end developer of the AVNIDA ad portal.

Developer, MTur - UFAL /CNPq - IFAL

2015 - 2019

Developer of educational mobile applications (Android/UWP) and for accessible tourism (Android/iOS) in projects financed by the Brazilian Ministry of Tourism and CNPq.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree in progress, Federal University of Alagoas (UFAL)

Maceió/AL

Aug 2020 — Present

Currently studying the sixth period of the bachelor's degree in computer engineering

Technician, Federal Institute of Alagoas (IFAL)

Arapiraca/AL

Jan 2013 — Jan 2017

Computer Technician

COURSES

Vue.js developer, .NET developer, Front-end engineer, UX designer and Code versioning with Git, ALURA

2018

AWARDS

HackaFlag Winner

Maceió/AL

2017

Winner of the Maceió stage of HackaFlag, the largest CTF in Latin America.